http://www.getty.edu/legal/privacy.html

Organizational Chart
Education Dept.
Field Projects Dept.
Science Dept.
AATA Online
Project Bibliographies (searchable)
GCI e–Bulletin
Multimedia (videos & slideshows)
GCI Reference Collection (for materials analysis)
More Ways to Search
!
Privacy Policy
The J. Paul Getty Trust is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not collect your personal information, such as your name, mailing address, or e-mail address, unless you knowingly provide it to us.
Most pages of our Web site contain a link to this privacy policy, which describes what information we collect and how we use it. By using any Getty Web site or app or communicating with us by e-mail, you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.
General Policy on Collection of Information
We only collect personally identifiable information if you knowingly provide it to us.
We may record your e-mail address if you e-mail us, submit an online form that contains your e-mail address, opt to receive e-mail notices of Getty programs, news, and events, or register for an online service such as Getty Bookmarks or the Teacher Art Exchange discussion board.
We will never share your e-mail address with anyone.
Our systems automatically records the IP addresses of visitors to our site. This information is used in aggregate form to helps us understand how visitors use the Getty online environment. The servers at this site also collect connection-related technical data. The data entries in these logs are used for server and network operation and maintenance and to help us understand general usage patterns.
Blogs
The Getty provides blogs on this site. You are welcome to post comments to these blogs. You may post comments anonymously or under your name or alias. Names and aliases are publicly displayed. We do not sell or share commenters' names or e-mail addresses; we do save commenters' e-mail addresses and will use them only to contact you if we have questions about or direct replies to the contents of your comments.
E-Cards
Some pages on this site allow you to send free e-cards to a friend. E-cards are sent as links to a Getty.edu Web page. We do not sell or share senders' or recipients' names or e-mail addresses; we do save e-mail addresses and we will use them only to contact you if necessary.
E-Newsletters
The Getty offers free electronic newsletters sent via e-mail.
To receive an e-newsletter by e-mail, you need to submit your name, zip code, and email address. Your personal information is stored on secure servers. When you sign up, you can choose to receive the e-newsletters in HTML, which includes graphics, or as text only, which does not include graphics.
You can view the e-Getty newsletter online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/egetty/e-getty.html.
You can view GRI e-News online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/egetty/grievents/index.html.
You can view GCI e-Bulletin online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/conservation/publications/bulletin/current.html.
You can view Exploring Antiquity online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/egetty/villa/index.html.
You can view Getty Foundation News online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/foundation/news/foundation_news/current.html.
You can view ArtBound: New Books from the Getty online, without submitting your e-mail address, at http://www.getty.edu/museum/publications/art_bound/current.html.
You may stop receiving e-newsletters at any time. Follow the "unsubscribe" link in the footer of any newsletter.
On Demand Text Messages
From time to time we may invite visitors with SMS-enabled mobile devices to request information or offers by texting a keyword to a short code, for example, "To access a mobile phone tour of Sample Exhibition, text sample to 12345." If you respond to this kind of call to action, we will immediately send you a one-time text message with the information you requested. We will not send you recurring text messages, and we will not retain your information any longer than reasonably necessary to fulfill your request. We will never share your information with any third parties.
Online Surveys
We may occasionally ask you to participate in surveys appearing on various pages of this site. Your participation in these surveys is voluntary. These surveys may ask for information relating to your background, occupation, or experience, or ask for identifying information such as an email address. We use this information to help us better understand and respond to the needs of our audiences and to enhance our marketing efforts.
Getty Bookmarks
To use the Getty Bookmark feature, you need to create an online account. Your e-mail address is used to identify your account and the associated bookmarks. The e-mail address tied to your account is stored on secure Getty servers and will not be used for marketing purposes or shared with anyone. We may occasionally use your e-mail address for purposes related to administration of your online account, such as sending service notices or password reminders.
We use cookies to administer your online account(s). However, we do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information.
If you choose to e-mail Getty Bookmarks to a friend, we will ask you for your friend's e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail containing your bookmarks, but we will not store his or her e-mail address or use it for any other purpose.
You may review or change the password(s) for your online account(s) at any time. Log in to Getty Bookmarks and click "Edit Profile" to choose a new password.
You may contact us at bookmarks@getty.edu to request that we remove your e-mail address from our database.
Planning a School Visit
To request a school visit to the Getty, you must submit information about yourself, your school, and the nature of your visit request. This information is used to help us accommodate school visit requests as equitably as possible. The information is recorded and stored in a database by our Education Department and may be used to contact you. We periodically send information to schools and teachers to notify them of additions to our Web site and of new educational programs at the Getty.
If you no longer wish to receive mailings from the Education Department, please call the school line at (310) 440-7322.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
A cookie is a piece of data we store on your computer's hard drive. This data contains information about you that we use to help make your visit to the Getty website easier. For example, one cookie we may store can remember what kind of video capability you have selected, so that you do not have to choose a bandwidth every time you watch a video. In addition, we have authorized various reputable companies to help us track cookies so that we can analyze how people are using the Getty website in order to continually offer the best possible experience for our visitors.
Pixel tags are small pieces of code that may place cookies or provide non personally-identifiable information such as IP address, time of website visit, or browser used.
In addition, the Getty engages third-party service providers who use cookies and pixel tags on our behalf.
See "Third-Party Service Providers," below.
Neither the Getty nor any of the companies we work with will collect personally-identifiable information using cookies or pixel tags.
You do not have to accept any Getty cookies to enjoy and use the Getty website; if you reject all Getty cookies you will simply have to re-enter the preferences that we would otherwise record for you.
Your iOS or Android device may provide a "Limit Ad Tracking" or "Opt out of interest-based advertising" setting that you can enable if you would like to limit ad tracking from pixel tags on mobile devices.
Third-Party Service Providers
The Getty engages reputable third-party vendors in order to help us manage the Getty website and mobile applications, process transactions, better respond to the needs of our visitors, and enhance our marketing efforts. This includes third-party e-commerce service providers who collect personal information necessary to process transactions, and may use the collected information to improve the services they provide. It also includes third-party marketing partners who serve advertisements across the Internet and sometimes on the Getty website and mobile applications on the Getty's behalf. These marketing partners may use information about your visits to the Getty website and mobile applications and other sites to personalize advertisements.
Links to Other Web Sites
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the Getty. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies only to this Web site.
Children Under 13 Years of Age
Unless otherwise explicitly stated, Web sites and apps maintained by the Getty are not specifically dedicated to children and we do not actively solicit information from children. Children age 12 or under must obtain permission from a parent or guardian before submitting information to this Web site.
Changes in This Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. Please visit this page periodically to check our current policy.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at web@getty.edu.
Effective Date: June 30, 2011 (last updated June 7, 2018)
